pwedeh.com 2016-06-24

# PRIVACY POLICY | PHILIPPINE PCSO LOTTO RESULTS PCSO

**Pwedeh.com respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Pwedeh.com.

**Credit card details**

Pwedeh.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Pwedeh.com.

**External Sites.**

Pwedeh.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Pwedeh.com to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Pwedeh.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Pwedeh.com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Pwedeh.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email at: enterjasper@yahoo.com

**SITE REMINDERS:**

Posting of phone numbers and other contact information is currently restricted on this site. This is due to reports of scams resulting from such monetary schemes to lure unsuspecting readers in exchange of some trivial and often malicious services. 

Offending and disrespectful remarks are also prohibited on the merits of maintaining the site from cyberbullying and any form of profanity, as well as to promote positive and healthy interaction among our readers and followers alike. 

Use original username/codename (not fullname). Username/Codename must not be the same as your e-mail address. 

Content post must be in a horizontal form. 

Deletion/Banned will be imposed at any time without prior notice.

.................................................................................................................
